A Guide to the Genealogical Bureau of Virginia, 1923-1945
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Genealogical Bureau of Virginia, 1923-1945
The Library of Virginia
52989
15.45 cubic feet (31 boxes)
Trenton Hizer
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Joel P. Cocks, Richmond, Virginia, and William L. Lawrence, Gloucester, Virginia.
Historical Information
The Genealogical Bureau of Virginia was founded by William Macfarlane Jones (1868-1951). The Bureau conducted genealogical research in Virginia records for clients.
Scope and Content
Records, 1923-1945, of the Genealogical Bureau of Virginia, located in Richmond, Virginia, consisting of abstracts of deeds, wills, birth, marriage, and death records; correspondence, genealogical charts and notes; research records, and other documents detailing the Bureau's genealogical research for clients regarding ancestors who lived in Virginia. Genealogical research was often conducted to assist clients interested in membership in societies like the Daughters of the American Revolution or the Sons of the American Revolution.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged
Series I: Family files
Series II: Client files
Series III: General records
Series IV: Non-Bureau records
Contents List
- Series I: Family files., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 1-4)
  Family files consist of genealogical research on various families and is arranged alphabetically. Records contain information on births, deaths, marriages, and family relations.
  - Family files A Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Family files B (Ba) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Family files B (Be) Oversize item located in Box 28, Folder 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Family files B (Bi-Bl) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Family files B (Bland) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Family files B (Bo) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Family files B (Br) Oversize item located in Box 28, Folder 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Family files B (Bracey, Bressie, etc.) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Family files B (Bu-By) Oversize item located in Box 28, Folder 3 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Family files C (Ca) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 3 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Family files C (Ce-Cl) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 4 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Family files C (Co) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 2 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Family files C (Cr-Cu)Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 5 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Family files D (Da-De) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Family files D (Di-Du) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 6 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Family files E Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 7 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Family files F (Fa-Fl) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 8 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Family files F (Fo) Oversize item located in Box 28, Folder 4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Family files F (Fr) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 9 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Family files G (Ga-Gl) Oversize item located in Box 28, Folder 5 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Family files G (Go-Gw) Oversize item located in Box 28, Folder 6 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Family files H (Hac-Han) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 10 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Family files H (Har-Hax) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 3 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Family files H (Harrison) (folder 1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Family files H (Harrison) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Family files H (He-Hi) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 11 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Family files H (Ho-Hu) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 12 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Family files I (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Family files J Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 4 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Family files K (Ka-Ko) Oversize item located in Box 28, Folder 7 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Family files K (Kuykendall) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Family files L (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Family files L (Langley) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Family files M (Mab-Man) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 13 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Family files M (Mapp) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Family files M (Mar-May) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 5 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Family files M (Mc) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 6 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Family files M (Me) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Family files M (Mi) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Family files M (Mo-Mu) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Family files N Oversize item located in Box 28, Folder 8 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Family files N (Nicholson) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Family files O (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Family files P (Pa) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Family files P (Pe) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 7 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Family files P (Pi-Pu) Oversize item located in Box 28, Folder 9 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Family files Q (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Family files R (Ra-Ri) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 8 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Family files R (Ro-Ru) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 14 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Family files S (Sa-Se) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 15 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Family files S (Sh-Sl) Oversize item located in Box 28, Folder 10 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Family files S (Sm-Sy) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 16 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Family files T (Ta-Te) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 9 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Family files T (Th-Ti) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Family files T (To-Tw) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 17 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Family files U-V Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 18 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Family files W (Wade) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Family files W (Wal) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Family files W (War-Wau) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 10 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Family files W (We-Wh) Oversize item located in Box 28, Folder 11 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Family files W (Wi) Oversize item located in Box 28, Folder 12 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Family files W (Wo-Wy) Oversize item located in Box 28, Folder 13 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Family files W (Woodson) (folder 1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Family files W (Woodson) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Family files Y (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Series II: Client files., Extent: 18 boxes. (Box 5-22)
  Client files consist of genealogical research conducted for clients of the Bureau. Records are organized by client number created by the Bureau. Records contain information on births, deaths, marriages, and family relations. No client files numbered 56, 96, 235, 237-300.
  - Client file 1: Mrs. Robert S. Lovett (family: Abercrombie) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 19 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Client file 2: Thalia G. Kelley (family: Houston, Graham, Seaborn, Black, Ackerman) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 20 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Client file 3: Mrs. Bryant (family: Harris, Adams, Field, Henderson, Sone, Lynch, Young, Clark, Goode, Jefferson, Miller, Hatcher, Jordan, Todd, Cocke) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Client file 4: ----- Snead (family: Snead, Buckner, Crump, Walker) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Client file 5: George H. Beers (family: Beers) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 21 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Client file 6: ----- Hobson (family: Hobson) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 11 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Client file 7: Henry Irving Buchannon (family: Buchanan)--empty file (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Client file 8: (family: Anderson, Jordan, Throckmorton, Blair, Moncure, Jordan, Bradford, Taylor) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Client file 9: James Blythe Anderson (family: Cannon, Harris, Sydnor, Jefferson, Crenshaw) Oversize item located in Box 29, Folder 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Client file 9A: Willard Reynolds Matheny (family: Matheny) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Client file 10: Austin Brockenbrough (family: Brockenbrough, Ragland, Chandler, Riddle, Tompkins, Call, Burruss) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 12 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Client file 11: Mrs. Gardner L. Boothe (family: Harrison, Trezevant, Daniel, Baylor, Henry, Armistead, Todd) (folder 1 of 2) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 22 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Client file 11: Mrs. Gardner L. Boothe (family: Harrison, Trezevant, Daniel, Baylor, Henry, Armistead, Todd) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Client file 12: ----- Bowe (family: Bowe, Griffin, Ragland, Davis, Muse, Potts) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Client file 13: Julia Hite Gallaher (family: Caldwell, Scott, Todd, Hackett, Herndon, Withers) (Captain John Caldwell--DAR, Captain John Scott--Colonial Dames) (folder 1 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Client file 13: Julia Hite Gallaher (family: Caldwell, Scott, Todd, Hackett, Herndon, Withers) (Captain John Caldwell--DAR, Captain John Scott--Colonial Dames) (folder 2 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Client file 13: Julia Hite Gallaher (family: Caldwell, Scott, Todd, Hackett, Herndon, Withers) (Captain John Caldwell--DAR, Captain John Scott--Colonial Dames) (folder 3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Client file see file 13: (family: Caldwell, Courtney) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Client file 14: Oliver P. Robinson (family: Robinson, McKay, Gwathmey, Temple, Gee, Elliott) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Client file 15: Elliston H. Bell (family: Bell) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Client file 16: Bernard Hoskins Baylor (family: Baylor) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 23 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Client file 17: Mrs. Louis Hankins (family: Waddill, Spencer, Kyle, Perry) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Client file 18: (family: Maddox, Humphries) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Client file 19: Charles T. Norman (family: Norman, Mosby) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Client file 20: W. W. Sale (family: Sale, Selden, Mason, Marable) Oversize item located in Box 29, Folder 2 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Client file 21: Clarence Earl Fleming (family: Fleming, Stanard, Caldwell, Spriggs, Cresap) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Client file 22: R. S. Robertson (family: Robertson, Archer, Anderson, Daniels, Gooch, Chiles, Eppes) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Client file Note: out of 22: (family: Nelson) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Client file 23: T. F. Turley (family: Turley) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Client file 24: Mrs. Newton H. Smith (family: Stratton, Batte, DeJarnette, Pemberton, Jennings, Stainback) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 24 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Client file 25: (family: Langley)--empty file (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Client file 26: Mrs. A. S. Burleson (family: Custis, Bacon, Andrews, Bugg, Parke, Pennington) Oversize item located in Box 29, Folder 3 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Client file 27: Grover Clayton Davis (family: Kemp, Taliaferro) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 25 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Client file 28: Mrs. Robert Marstello Peek (family: Wynn, Winn, Fowke, Branch) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Client file 29: James W. Marshall (family: Smyth, Williams) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Client file 30: Robert J. Travis (family: Farrell, Drew, Meaux, Darracott) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Client file 31: Mrs. H. H. Hardin(family: Arnold, Callaway, Jones, Hardin) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 26 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Client file 32: Cecil W. Vest (family: Vest, Lipscomb, Price, Black, Phipps) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Client file 33: Rebecca Key Bagby (family: Key) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Client file 34: (family: Trueheart)--empty file (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Client file 35: Emma Whitfield (family: Whitfield) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Client file 36: Mrs. Robert F. Miller (family: Miller, Ferguson) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 27 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Client file 37: Mrs. E. W. Newman, Fannie D. Frazier (family: Dickinson, Timberlake, Newman) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 28 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Client file 38: Mrs. B. W. Rhame (family: Lee, Lowry, Miller) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 29 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Client file 39: Mrs. L. P. Evans (family: Gannaway, Pate) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Client file 40: Mrs. C. C. Coleman, Jerome Carr, Mrs. John B. Garden (family: Carr, Moore, Boxley, Mansfield, Evans, Taylor) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 13 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Client file 41: E. L. Wheless (family: Hobson, Hatcher, McLaurine, Frayser, Spicer) Oversize item located in Box 29, Folder 4 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Client file 42: Albert Yoder (family: Brown, Miller) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Client file 43: (family: Vest, Jeffress, Moseley, Finch) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Client file 44: Mrs. M. A. Chambers (family: Edloe, Carter, Jackson, Browne, Foster) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Client file 45: George C. Gregory (family: Gregory, Osborne, Tanner) Oversize item located in Box 29, Folder 5 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Client file 46: (family: Oldham, Beville, Neville, Blakemore, Goodrich, Pemberton) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 30 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Client file 47: Mr. Colburn (family: Twiford, Twyford, Hatcher, Walters, Coleburn) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Client file 48: Mrs. K. I. Reed (family: Giles, Burton, Moore) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 31 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Client file 49: Mrs. Anna A. Crane (family: Crane, Craine, Henderson, Anderson, Lewis) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Client file 49A: Robert Isham Randolph (family: Randolph) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 14 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Client file 50: Myron E. Bristow (family: Griffith, Dickinson, Mayo) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 32 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Client file 51: William H. Parker (family: Parker, Batte) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 33 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Client file 52: Hardy and Page (family: Wyville, Danby) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Client file 53: Charles A. Weaver (family: Randolph, Jefferson) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Client file 54: Arthur W. Norton (family: Aylett, Winston, Jordan, Meredith) Oversize item located in Box 25, Folder 34 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Client file 55: John Shelton, Thomas Shelton (family: Shelton) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Client file 57: E. E. Holland and L. P. Holland (family: Holland, Lee, Everett) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Client file 58: Harry F. Byrd (family: Byrd, Flood, Ruffin, Cooke) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Client file 59: Jesse Hinton Binford (family: Binford, Mosby, Netherland) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Client file 60: Edwin Porch (family: Beale, Henry, Netherland, Woodson, Vance, Dudley, Hite) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Client file 61: John M. Taylor, Grace Taylor, Jennie Durham (family: Durham, Taylor) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Client file 62: Mary Winston Ivey (family: Ivey) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Client file 63: Carrie Smith, Mrs. James Woods (family: Woods, Smith, Davis, McNary, Shumate, Cardwell) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 1 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Client file 64: William Turley Hall (family: Harmon, Walker) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 2 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Client file 65: Mrs. A. Hankins (family: Guy, Lecky, Wortham, Ware) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 3 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Client file 66: T. H. Gurney, Mrs. M. C. Harding (family: Valentine, Quarles, Ellett) Oversize item located in Box 29, Folder 6 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Client file 67: J. J. Valentine, Mrs. C. W. Johns (family: Hall, Hodges, Brooks, Butt, Benthall) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 4 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Client file 68: Mrs. H. T. Vories[?] (family: Withers, Caldwell)--empty file (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Client file 69: Mary Pugh (family: Pugh) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Client file 70: (family: Booth, Massie)--empty file (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Client file 71: Ivy Vinton Marable Jeter (family: Jeter, Clough, Marable, Nelson, Piersey, Austin) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 15 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Client file 72: Sylvanus Stokes Bible record (family: Stokes) (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Client file 73: Wallace Hawkins (family: Henry) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Client file 74: T. G. Tinsley (family: Tinsley, Robson, Turner, Bohannon, Rawles) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 5 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Client file 75: Mrs. E. E. Moffett, Mrs. H. W. Jackson (family: Stokes, Woodson, Knight) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Client file 76: Mrs. E. A. Sterling (family: Poythress) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 16 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Client file 77: Paul Houchins (family: Houchins, Bowe, Dew) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Client file 78: Evelyn Lee Terrill (family: Lee) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 6 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Client file 79: W. J. Crowe (family: Magill, Evans, Crowe, Lacky) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Client file 80: Stuart Alexander Morgan (family: Austin, Cobbs, Morgan) (folder 1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Client file 80: Stuart Alexander Morgan (family: Austin, Cobbs, Morgan) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Client file 81: Herman S. Sidener (family: Geisensieder, Sidener) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Client file 82: (family: Bland, George, Dudley) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Client file 83: Mrs. C. S. Boxley (family: Curley, Johnson, Stewart) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folders 7-8 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Client file 84: Mrs. W. C. Saunders (family: Holdsworth) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Client file 85: Joseph Armstrong (family: Armstrong, Glascock, Glasscock) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 9 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Client file 86: Susie W. Cocke, Mrs. James T. Sloan (family: Austin, Brown, Timberlake, Hutcheson) Oversize item located in Box 29, Folder 7 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Client file 87: Mrs. Charles L. Alexander (family: Burwell) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 10 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Client file 88: Albert R. Erskine (family: Erskine) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Client file 89: Mrs. H. S. T. Henderson (family: Atwell, Pollard, Mitchell, Henderson, Turner, Byrd) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 11 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Client file 90: John Garland Pollard (family: Pollard) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Client file 91: John P. Pryor (family: Pryor) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 12 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Client file 92: W. E. Barrett (family: West, Scarborough, Barrett) Oversize item located in Box 29, Folder 8 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Client file 93: Julius C. Martin (family: Martin) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 13 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Client file 94: Harrison J. Price (family: Price, Bonner, Corley) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 14 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Client file 95: R. H. Williams, J. E. Williams (family: Williams, Berkeley, Carter) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 15 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Client file 97: Mrs. R. F. Simmons (family: Nicholas, Fry, Fontaine, Ballard, Scott, Porter, Simmons, Carter) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 16 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Client file 98: Mrs. A. W. Patterson (family: Pettus, Dillard) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 17 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Client file 99: Annie Stokes Adams (family: Stokes, Hayne, Anderson, Carter) (folder 1 of 2) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 18 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Client file 99: Annie Stokes Adams (family: Stokes, Hayne, Anderson, Carter) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Client file 100: Clarence D. Guess (family: Guess, Guest, Douglass, Bean) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Client file 101: Blair Taylor, John M. Taylor (family: Taylor, Pendleton) Oversize item located in Box 29, Folder 9 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Client file 102: Mrs. Rienzi Hobson Vance (family: Vance) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Client file 103: Mrs. W. L. Parsons (family: Andrews) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 19 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Client file 104: Rosa V. Hamilton (family: Hamilton, Edwards, Carr, Ragland, Wyatt, Waughopp, Fryer, Hancock) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 20 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Client file 105: Mrs. John F. Barnhill (family: Terrell, Parrott) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 21 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Client file 106: Mary Beaumont Gracey (family: Beaumont, Gracey) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 17 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Client file 107: R. V. Downing (family: Downing, Edwards, Saunders, Hughlett, Nutt, Lee) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 18 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Client file 108: Mrs. Gordon G. Heiner (family: Todd, Cloyd) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Client file 109: Mrs. L. W. Payne, Jr. (family: Bledsoe) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 19 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Client file 110: Blanche A. Swope (family: Carroll, Heth) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Client file 111: James D. Evans (Nicholson, Lee, Griggs, Hay) Oversize item located in Box 29, Folder 10 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Client file 112: Mrs. W. R. Williams (family: Powell) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Client file 113: Mrs. Lysle Withington (family: Hale, Nelson, Stone, Gentry, Burwell, Walker) Oversize item located in Box 29, Folder 11 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Client file 114: Mrs. O. B. Colquitt (family: Colquitt) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 22 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Client file 115: Mrs. F. W. Poindexter, Mrs. W. T. Dimm (family: Armistead, Burwell, Smith, Addison, Walker, Keith) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 23 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Client file 116: Frances Waddill Pofford, Mary Moton Freeman (family: Freeman, Garrett, Jones, Self) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 24 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Client file 117: Mrs. W. E. Wallace (family: Martin, Martain, Howell, Whitworth) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Client file 118: Walter Lee Sams (family: Foster, Burford, Lee, Sams) (folder 1 of 2) Oversize item located in Box 29, Folder 12 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Client file 118: Walter Lee Sams (family: Foster, Burford, Lee, Sams) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Client file 119: Mrs. A. T. Armstrong (family: Maxwell, Bland, Pemberton) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 25; Box 29 Folder 13 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Client file 120: Cary Nelson Weisiger (family: Weisiger, Isham, Hatcher, Martin) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 26 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Client file 121: James F. White, Mrs. B. W. Rawles, John B. Nicklen (family: White) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 27 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Client file 122: ----- Waller (family: Waller) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Client file 123: Helena Dismukes (family: Morrissett) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 28 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Client file 124: Alfred D. Amant (family: Weaver, Grimes, Henderson, Burnet, Parker, White, Cheatham) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Client file 125: J. R. Moll (family: Crutcher, Crenshaw) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Client file 126: Benjamin Harrison Turner (family: Massie, Claiborne, Mosby, Pendleton) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Client file 127: Robert Stewart Sanders (family: Sanders, Waters, Holladay, Fore) Oversize item located in Box 30, Folder 1 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Client file 128: Mrs. G. T. W. Kern (family: Wood, Kelly, Massie)--empty file (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Client file 129: B. W. Wilson (family: Wilson) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Client file 130: F. M. Hudson, R. A. Josey (family: Hudson, Josey, Riddle, Cotton, Booker) (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Client file 131: J. G. Glass (family: Glass, Gooch, Hart, Snead) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 29 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Client file 132: (family: Durrett) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Client file 133: Mrs. C. H. Dorsett (Sallie Crump) (family: Crump) (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Client file 134: Mrs. Robert K. Meade (family: Haskins, Weisiger, Minge, Harrison, Dandridge, Watkins) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 30 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Client file 135: R. L. Rankin (family: Brent, Baker, Carter, Edmonds, Fitzhugh, Payne) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Client file 136: R. H. Grinstead (family: Grinstead) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Client file 137: Ruth Murray (family: Beale, Bedford) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 31 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Client file 138: Clifton M. Miller (family: Miller) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Client file 139: Junius E. West (family: West, Berriman, Darden) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Client file 140: Mrs. H. E. Ellett (family: Ellett, Pemberton, Mosby, Quarles, Spears) (folder 1 of 2) Oversize item located in Box 30, Folder 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)